HEATHER WARREN

253.861.2712 heathwa1@uw.edu

Dedicated and highly skilled customer service specialist with 15+ years of industry experience. Outstanding ability to navigate ever-changing workflows of business needs with a passion for exceeding expectations of required duties to enhance the guest experience.

- ✓ Dispute Resolution
- ✓ Problem Solving
- ✓ Adaptability
- ✓ Collaborative Teamwork

- ✓ Leadership & Training
- ✓ Multitasking/Organizational Ability
- ✓ Communication Skills
- ✓ ArcGIS Technical Training

KEY SKILL AREAS

MANAGEMENT - Created and implemented hiring and training procedures for onboarding of new employees for successful development of job skills. Coordinated schedules of 10+ employees to efficiently meet business levels of a restaurant and entertainment venue. Resolved complaints from guests to ensure a positive experience during their visit.

ORGANIZATIONAL SKILLS - Coordinated special requests for professional events including seating arrangements, decorating and menu selection for accommodating 10 to 100+ guests. Organized and maintained clear communication to ensure complete guest satisfaction.

COMMUNICATION - Effectively communicated with guests and employees, often clarifying through inquiry, to achieve complete comprehension of the needs of each. Provided exceptional customer service by creating a memorable experience often exceeding the expectations of both guests as well as those from management.

TECHNICAL TRAINING – Engaged in technical training in ArcGIS to utilize statistical analysis paired with spatial data to create a functional visual representation through the computer-based program. Developed working knowledge of audiovisual equipment for multimedia room including projectors, HDMI functions and different receiver functions.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Arts in Sustainable Urban Development, Minor in Environmental Studies University of Washington, Tacoma 2018 - 2020 Coursework:

Understanding the origins of complex processes of development of metropolitan areas, focusing on the impact of urbanization on social and ecological systems both internally and as part of a global system.

Examination of how socioeconomic status, human preference, and ecological politics affect ecosystem services and influence the creation of urban policies.

Map interpretation with ArcGIS spatial analysis through geographical information systems as well as urban research methods and statistical urban analysis.

Geographic Information Systems (GIS) Certificate 2020

Associates in Arts and Science, Tacoma Community College, 2018

General coursework with a focus in Social Sciences of Psychology, Sociology, and Anthropology

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

HOTEL MURANO, Tacoma, WA

2014-Present

Restaurant Server

- Execute effective time management and organizational practices while professionally greeting and accurately obtaining orders for 24+ guests arriving at varying times.
- Create a personalized experience by engaging in conversation and addressing those by name who visit on more than one occasion.
- Practice discretion and respect the privacy of those guests who may be well known yet wish to remain anonymous during their visit.
- Provide meals through detailed communication of dietary restrictions, allergies, and accommodating special requests as well as prepare and provide adult beverages with proper verification of valid identification.
- Carefully follow proper payment procedures upon completion of the visit through credit card authorization, providing correct change or by verifying room information for room charges.

- > Coordinate duties with coworkers to ensure necessary supplies are replenished throughout the shift to maintain successful and seamless transition through varying business levels.
- > Recognized as Employee of the Quarter in 2015 leading to Employee of the Year in 2015.

STEEL CREEK AMERICAN WHISKEY, CO, Tacoma, WA

2013-2015

Restaurant Server

- Engaged in customer interaction upon entrance to the restaurant through the conclusion of the visit.
- ➤ Increased sales through extensive knowledge of current specials and daily events.
- Managed accuracy of orders for food and beverage of individual guests in parties of 30+ people.

VARSITY GRILLL, Tacoma, WA

2005-2013

Restaurant Supervisor

- ➤ Built and adjusted weekly schedule for a staff of 10+ to meet the variation of business levels.
- > Participated in hiring process and developed a training program for all new employees including standards for business operations and opening and closing procedures.
- ➤ Replied to inquiries and coordinated planning for private events including menu selection and appropriate venue space. Applied sincere dispute resolution strategies through active listening and problem-solving skills to ensure guest satisfaction.
- > Operated audio-visual equipment for different viewing capacities as well as troubleshooted technical issues.

GENE JUAREZ SALONS AND SPA, Tukwila, WA

2003-2005

Front Desk Supervisor

- > Supervised a staff of 7+ employees ensuring proper break schedules, business procedures and cash handling procedures were adhered to.
- ➤ Educated in all services Gene Juarez offered to schedule appropriately for new and returning guests. Offered relevant services in addition to enhance guest experience and increase sales for the service provider.
- Accurate cash handling skills for deposits of \$10,000+ dollars and necessary change requests for business levels.
- > Protected privacy of guests and services received and sensitive personal information.